



DANIELA PEREIRA

Date of birth: 30/03/1981Nationality: Portuguese, BrazilianSex:

FemaleMobile number: (+351) 915319341 (Mobile) Email address:

dani.mpereira@gmail.com Facebook:

https://www.facebook.com/dmendespereira LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniela-mendes-pereira-a4666924/

Skype: dani.mp30

Address: Av. Doutor Lourenço Peixinho, 3800-162, Aveiro, Portugal (Home)

About me

I'm Portuguese-Brazilian and have been living in Portugal for almost 5 years. I currently work as a Sales Consultant in Aveiro. In Brazil, I worked in administration, education and quality control. My characteristics include: adaptability, good humour, dynamism, initiative, responsibility, focus, dedication to work and good interpersonal relationships.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

01/10/2018 - ATUAL Aveiro, Portugal

COMMERCIAL CONSULTANT IMOFACIL SOCIEDADE IMOBILIÁRIA LDA

- 1. Administrative and customer service work;
- 2. Prospecting and attracting new products,
- 3. Real estate brokerage,
- 4. Creative Problem Solving.

06/06/2017 - 17/08/2018 Goiânia, Brazil

PEDAGOGICAL ADVISOR COLÉGIO VISÃO

- Pedagogical Consultancy (Management and Pedagogical Coordination) drawing up class timetables, helping to develop pedagogical projects, communicating with and attending to parents and students, reviewing bimonthly assessments, enrolling new students.
- 2. Support for the psychology department;
- 3. Creation and editing of digital media (videos);

10/01/2016 - 10/01/2017 Goiânia, Brazil

CEABA PEDAGOGICAL COORDINATOR

- Analysing, organising and approving the activities and content taught to the children;
- Attending to parents, students and teachers;
- · Management and selection of new teachers.

06/06/2012 - 03/02/2015 Campinas, Brazil

EAD PEDAGOGICAL COORDINATOR ANHANGUERA EDUCAIONAL

1. Preparing, reviewing and making available training courses for the professionals working at the face-to-face support centres: Coordinators and Tutors;

PEDAGOGICAL MANAGER MIND LAB GROUP BRAZIL

- 1. Training teachers in the "Innovative Mind" methodology, which aims to use thinking games for the cognitive, emotional, ethical and social development of students and teachers;
- 2. Team management:
- Managing relationships between the company, schools and local councils on educational and administrative matters.

12/02/2002 - 14/04/2010 Campinas, Brazil

CHEMICAL TECHNICIAN MEDLEY INDUSTRIA FARMACÊUTICA (SANOFI GROUP)

- 1. From 2002 to 2007 Chemical analyses and physical tests on final products and raw materials;
- 2. From 2007 to 2010 Administrative manager of the Quality Control laboratory, involved in purchasing materials and supplies, data management, checking and analysing documentation, key user of the SAP system.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

10/01/2006 - 10/12/2010 Campinas, Brazil

PEDAGOGUE (SCIENCE OF EDUCATION) UNICAMP

Address Barão Geraldo, Campinas , Campinas , Brazil | Website www.unicamp.br

10/01/1996 - 20/12/1999 Campinas, Brazil

CHEMICAL TECHNICIAN ETECAP

Address Av. Cônego Antônio Roccato, s/n - Jardim Santa Monica, Campinas, Brazil

Website www.etecap.com.br

10/05/2015 - 27/06/2015 Toronto, Canada

BASIC ENGLISH Hansa Language Centre

Address Englinton Avenue, Toronto, Canada | Website https://hansacanada.com/home/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **PORTUGUESE**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTAND		SPEAK		WRITE
	Listening compreh	Readin	Oral productionOral interaction		
ENGLISH	ension A2	B1	A2	A2	A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Advanced user

DIGITAL COMPETENCES

Microsoft Office | Using the Internet as a communication, research and investigation tool | Microsoft Excel | Social networks Office PowerPoint | Office Word | ERP applications - SAP AdobePhotoshop Adobe Premiere Adobe Lightroom Adobe Illustrator Adobe Indesign

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving licence: B1

Driving licence: B

SOCIAL AND COMMUNICATION SKILLS

Competences

- 1. Microsoft Office (Word, Excel and Powerpoint) Excellent knowledge.
- 2. SAP Good knowledge Worked as Key User from 2008 to 2010.
- 3. Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Premiere Good knowledge. In 2016, he worked as a freelancer creating and editing videos for events such as weddings, christenings and birthdays.
- 4. Social skills: good relationship with the whole team, respects hierarchical level, knows how to debate and put forward their point of view in a correct and healthy way. Prioritises respect and kindness in relationships with colleagues, bosses and clients.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Personal Information

- 1. She is married and has a 9-year-old daughter.
- 2. He lived in Toronto (Canada) for 3 months (2015).
- 3. You have your own car.
- 4. Willing to move to another city or country.
- 5. She can be contacted by phone, SMS, e-mail or whatsapp.